extremeskins.com 2014-03-27

# Redskins.com | Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the Washington Redskins' website located at [www.redskins.com](http://prod.www.redskins.clubs.nfl.com/) (collectively the "Site"), which is operated by Pro-Football, Inc. (collectively, the "PROVIDERS", "we", "our", or "us"). The purpose of this privacy policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.

##### Types of Information that may be Collected

The following are the types of information we may collect:

###### Information You Provide Us

Personal information that you provide to us, such as your user ID and password, name, email address, telephone number, credit card, account number, physical address, birth date, gender or zip code or other information may be collected via the Site.

###### Site Usage Information

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit the Site. For example, we may collect click-stream data and your IP address.

###### Email Communications

When you open emails from the Site, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened an email from us, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from us and our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what types of emails you have opted to and not to receive.

###### Information from Other Sources

We may receive information about you from other sources and add it to your personal information.

##### how information may be collected

We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Site, including but not limited to those described below:

###### Registration

You You may be asked first to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Site may choose to offer, including, but not limited to, newsletters, contests, forums, fantasy or other subscription-based services.

All users must register when shopping at the Redskins Online Store site ([http://store.redskins.com](http://store.redskins.com/)). Our registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name, age range, password, and e-mail address). You must be 13 years of age or older to register. Registration helps us to provide you with an easy and personalized shopping experience, with quick and simple checkout options. The customer contact information you supply on the registration form will be used to send you e-mail newsletters and updates about upcoming sales, contests, promotions and product information. In addition, the information is used, when necessary, to contact you concerning the status of an order or to answer any of your questions. We may selectively choose to share this information with other divisions of our business and/or third parties.

At all times, you have the option of "opting out" of receiving future e-mail updates by visiting our choice/opt-out form.   
If you would like, you can also fill out a customer profile. While it is not required, information obtained from the customer profile questions helps us to learn more about our customers and is used to improve our customers' shopping experience with us.

###### Newsletters and Site Emails

We may offer free newsletters to share information with you about the Site, about us and our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our business partners and advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Site. You may cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided on the Site or, in some instances, in the designated area of certain newsletters or emails.

##### Contests or Sweepstakes

We may operate contests and sweepstakes through the Site which may require registration. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes. We may post publicly some of your information on the Site, such as on a winners page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. In some instances, a third party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Site, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we have no control over the information collected and accordingly urge you to review the advertiser's or sponsor's privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.

###### Surveys or Voting

From time-to-time we may request personally identifiable information from you via surveys or voting polls. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information. At times, you may have to register to vote or to take part in a survey.

###### Cookies

As with many websites, the Site uses standard technology called "cookies," which are small data files that are transferred to your computer when you allow your browser to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your web browser to the Site whenever you visit the Site, and make using the Site easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Site, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Site are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Site. Cookies may also allow the Site to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you generally can opt out of providing this information by turning the cookies off in your browser; however, some areas of the Site may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

###### IP Addresses and Click-stream Data

We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. Our computers identify your computer by its IP address. When you request web pages from the Site, our computers log your IP address. Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request web pages from the Site. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Site, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

###### Order Information

Customers use an order form to request or purchase information or products. When you place an order, we collect contact information, such as your shipping and e-mail addresses, and financial information, such as your account or credit card numbers. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about us to our customers and to get in touch with them when necessary. Financial information is used to bill the customer for products. You also have the option of ordering products over the telephone, and you may choose to pay by check.

If you register with the site, we can store your credit card information on file on our secure servers for your use on future orders. If you select this option, you will be able to store multiple credit card information in "My Account" of the Redskins Online Store. You will be shown the name you selected for your card, its last four digits, and the expiration date to confirm it is the card you want to use again. When you select this payment option, your credit card information goes over a secured server.

In order to change or modify information previously provided by you, please click on the Shop tab and then choose "My Account" and update your information using the options on this page.

##### How we use the Information Collected

Each of the PROVIDERS own the information collected via this Site. As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:

  * contact you about the Site;
  * contact you relating to your membership status;
  * confirm or fulfill an order you have made;
  * monitor or improve the use of the Site;
  * customize the advertising and content you see;
  * monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Site;
  * provide special offers to you from the PROVIDERS and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties;
  * send you promotional material on behalf of our business partners;
  * inform you of a prize you have won.

##### With whom the Information May be Shared

At times, we may share your personally identifiable information ("PII”) with others for various purposes. We will not share, sell, rent or trade PII with third parties for their promotional purposes. The following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others:

###### Agents

We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Site analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These entities have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

###### Promotional Offers

We may send offers by email to you on behalf of other parties. When we do this, we do not give that party your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, you may opt out in response to the email, or change your preferences by visiting ( http://prod.www.redskins.clubs.nfl.com/footer/privacy-policy/opt-out.html).

###### Aggregate Information

We may share aggregate information such as demographics and Site usage statistics with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

###### Opt-in and Opt-out Programs

Throughout the Site you may be presented with opportunities to receive special offers from third parties. An opt-in/opt-out message will ask you if you would like your information to be shared. If you do choose to have your information shared, in an effort to protect you, third parties who have access to personally identifiable information must abide by the current Site privacy policy. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other companies, and you should review the privacy practices of such Web sites prior to providing your personally identifiable information.

###### Third-Party Ad Serving

The Site may use a third party network advertiser to serve the advertisements on the Site. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to this Site and other Web sites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products or Web sites you might be interested in. Although advertisers or other companies do not have access to the Site cookies, the Site's advertisers and sponsors may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have your cookies enabled in your browser. Cookies allow third party advertisers to show you advertisements or content you might be interested in. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Please click here ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)) in order to learn more about the information collection practices and "opt-out" procedures of third party ad servers we may use.

###### Business Transfers

The Site or a PROVIDER may be sold along with its assets, or other transactions may occur in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred. In such a case, your personally identifiable information, which we have gathered, may be one of the business assets we transfer.

###### Legal Process

In the event we are required to respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process your personally identifiable information may be disclosed pursuant to such subpoena, court order or legal process, which may be without notice to you.

##### Tell-a-Friend

If If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Bridgeline Software stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [support@redskins.com](mailto:support@redskins.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

###### Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards

The Site may make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to its users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. The PROVIDERS cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.

###### Links to Other Web Sites

This privacy policy applies only to this Site. When you are on the Site you could be directed to other sites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Site onto a different web site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and others that may use the Site's logo as part of a cobranding agreement. These other web sites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to our Site, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

##### Security

This Site incorporates reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration. Certain personally identifiable information, such as credit card information, is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.

Redskins.com has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you provide. We encrypt your personal information, including your credit card number, when transmitting over the Internet between systems using encryption technology by PGP Corporation and a VeriSign SSL (Secure socket Layer), to safeguard your Internet transactions. PGP Corporation's Software Development Kit (SDK), has been used to encrypt and decrypt many petabytes of information worldwide. PGP technology and products have been proven in the field by more than a decade of use with many of the world's largest and most security-sensitive enterprises, government agencies and individuals.

VeriSign, Inc. is a leading provider of Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) and digital certificate solutions used by enterprises, Websites and consumers to conduct secure communications and transactions over the Internet and private networks..

Browsers that allow for SSL Technology Ordering from our Website require the use of an SSL-compliant browser, such as Netscape 4.0 or later; Microsoft Internet Explorer 5.0 or later; 5.0 AOL client for PCs; or the 5.0 AOL client for Macs. You will not be able to use Secure Mode if you have an older version of an Internet browser that does not support secure transactions, or if your computer is located on a local area network (LAN) that uses a firewall that prohibits secure transactions. If Secure Mode is not possible, please select one of our off-line options to place your order.

##### A Special Note for Parents Concerning Privacy

The Site is a general audience site. We do not currently collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen on the Site. If in the future, the PROVIDERS knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children, we will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) including, without limitation, obtaining necessary parental consents. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's Web site ([www.the-dma.org](http://www.the-dma.org/)) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise Web site ([www.getnetwise.org](http://www.getnetwise.org/)) to learn more about parental control tools.

##### Your Acceptance of the Privacy Policy and Notification of Changes to the Policy

By using this Website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our privacy policy. We may amend this privacy policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on our website and / or send an email to users who have provided an email address. We will assume that you have given your permission for your information to be used under the terms of the new privacy policy, if you do not respond to our email within thirty days or continue to use the Website thirty days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.

##### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information (such as your address) changes, or if you no longer desire to access our Site, you may correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us by making changes to your profile, by using an opt out message in an email, or by emailing member Sites at [webmaster@redskins.com](mailto:webmaster@redskins.com) with your request..

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of this Site, you can contact: [webmaster@redskins.com](mailto:webmaster@redskins.com)..

To change or modify information previously provided by you in the Redskins Online Store, please click on the Shop tab and then choose "My Account" and update your information using the options on this page.

##### Privacy

We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Advertisers using Spotlight tags are contractually obligated to disclose the use of pixels on their website. The text below is suggested disclosure language which should be posted on an advertiser's site along with any other related privacy disclosures: "Use of pixels, or transparent GIF files, is to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to ([ http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy))."

Redskins.com has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers information collected through this Web site, [www.redskins.com](http://www.redskins.com/) and [www.extremeskins.com](http://www.extremeskins.com/). TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please [click here to contact us](http://www.redskins.com/footer/contact-us.html) or call 703-726-7000. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

Pro-Football, Inc., Redskin Park, 21300 Redskin Park Drive, Ashburn, Virginia 20147
